
[
  {"question":"There are 60 classrooms at SPHS", "answer":true},
  {"question":"The new STEM building at SPHS will house the math classrooms currently in the bungalows and the biology classes", "answer":false},
  {"question":"In the movie Amadeus, Salieri is a made up character", "answer":false},
  {"question":"Mozart’s Requiem was never finished — ironically, Mozart died before its completion", "answer":true},
  {"question":"The four major violin concerti prior to 1900 are the Mendelssohn, Beethoven, Brahms, and Tchaikovsky concerti", "answer":true},
  {"question":"The Los Angeles Philharmonic is 150 years old", "answer":false},
  {"question":"A standard grand piano has 88 keys", "answer":true},
  {"question":"The longest symphony in the standard orchestral repertoire is Berlioz’s Symphonie Fantastique", "answer":false},
  {"question":"Walt Disney Concert Hall in downtown Los Angeles was originally not intended to be built with steel", "answer":true},
  {"question":"Haydn wrote a whopping 106 symphonies", "answer":true}
]
